<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">My City</string>
    <string name="category_parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="category_establishments">Establishments</string>
    <string name="category_museums">Museums</string>
    <string name="peace_park">Peace park</string>
    <string name="city_garden">City Garden</string>
    <string name="mud_park">MUD Park</string>
    <string name="jubilee_park">Jubilee Park</string>
    <string name="oleg_babayevs_square">Oleg Babayev\'s Square</string>
    <string name="kotlov_park">I.F. Kotlov Park</string>
    <string name="komsomolsky_park">Komsomolsky Park</string>
    <string name="peace_park_details">This is the largest park in Kremenchug. It was founded in 1897 and occupies an area of about 60 hectares. There are many trees, shrubs, flowers and fountains in the park. The park also has children\'s playgrounds, sports fields and amusement rides.</string>
    <string name="city_garden_details">This is a historical park located in the center of Kremenchug. It was founded in the 18th century and covers an area of about 10 hectares. There are many trees, shrubs and flowers in the park. The park also has playgrounds, sports grounds and fountains.</string>
    <string name="mud_park_details">It is a small park located in the left-bank part of Kremenchug. It was founded in the 19th century and occupies an area of about 5 hectares. There are many trees, bushes and flowers in the park. The park also has a playground and a fountain.</string>
    <string name="jubilee_park_details">It is a modern park located in the right-bank part of Kremenchug. It was founded in 1967 and occupies an area of about 30 hectares. The park has a variety of trees, shrubs and flowers. The park also has playgrounds, sports grounds and attractions.</string>
    <string name="oleg_babayevs_square_details">It is a small public garden located in the center of Kremenchug. It was founded in 2021 and occupies an area of about 1 hectare. There are a lot of trees, bushes and flowers in the park. There is also a children\'s playground and a fountain in the square.</string>
    <string name="kotlov_park_details">It is a park located in the left-bank part of Kremenchug. It was founded in 1960 and occupies an area of about 20 hectares. The park has a variety of trees, shrubs and flowers. The park also has playgrounds, sports grounds and attractions.</string>
    <string name="komsomolsky_park_details">It is a park located in the left-bank part of Kremenchug. It was founded in 1950 and occupies an area of about 15 hectares. The park has a variety of trees, shrubs and flowers. The park also has playgrounds, sports grounds and attractions.</string>
    <string name="local_history_museum">Local History Museum</string>
    <string name="aviation_and_cosmonautics_history_museum">Museum of History of Aviation and Cosmonautics</string>
    <string name="makarenko_house_museum">A.S. Makarenko House-Museum</string>
    <string name="odnostroyu_history_museum">Museum of Odnostroyu History</string>
    <string name="railroad_museum">Railroad Museum</string>
    <string name="military_equipment_museum">Museum of Military Equipment</string>
    <string name="art_gallery">Art Gallery</string>
    <string name="local_history_museum_details">It is one of the oldest museums in Ukraine. It was founded in 1879 and is dedicated to the history and culture of Kremenchug and Poltava region. The museum houses more than 100 thousand exhibits, including archaeological finds, works of art, documents and photographs</string>
    <string name="aviation_and_cosmonautics_history_museum_details">This is a museum dedicated to the history of aviation and cosmonautics. The museum displays airplanes, helicopters, rockets and other flying machines, as well as documents, photos and items related to the history of space exploration</string>
    <string name="makarenko_house_museum_details">This is a museum dedicated to the life and work of the outstanding educator Anton Semyonovich Makarenko. The museum presents documents, photographs, books and other exhibits related to Nazarenko\'s life and work</string>
    <string name="odnostroyu_history_museum_details">This is a museum dedicated to the history of military uniforms. The museum displays samples of military uniforms from different eras and countries, as well as documents, photographs and items related to the history of military uniforms</string>
    <string name="railroad_museum_details">This is a museum dedicated to the history and development of railway transportation. The museum presents layouts, models, photographs and other exhibits related to the history of railway transportation</string>
    <string name="military_equipment_museum_details">This is a museum dedicated to the history of military equipment. The museum displays samples of military equipment from different eras, as well as documents, photographs and items related to the history of military equipment</string>
    <string name="art_gallery_details">This is a gallery that presents works of art by artists of Poltava region. The gallery presents paintings, sculptures, graphics and other works of art</string>
    <string name="local_history_museum_work_time">9AM-4:30PM</string>
    <string name="aviation_and_cosmonautics_history_museum_work_time">9AM-6PM</string>
    <string name="makarenko_house_museum_work_time">8AM-3PM</string>
    <string name="odnostroyu_history_museum_work_time">9AM-6PM</string>
    <string name="military_equipment_museum_work_time">10AM-1PM, 2PM-6PM</string>
    <string name="art_gallery_work_time">10AM-5PM</string>
    <string name="ivushki_restaurant">Ivushki Restaurant</string>
    <string name="picasso_restaurant">Picasso Restaurant</string>
    <string name="cafe_kofan">Cafe Kofan</string>
    <string name="dao_noodle_bar_restaurant">Dao Noodle Bar Restaurant</string>
    <string name="four_seasons_restaurant">Four Seasons Restaurant</string>
    <string name="ivushki_restaurant_details">It is a restaurant specializing in Russian and Ukrainian cuisine. The restaurant is located in the city center and has a cozy atmosphere. The restaurant serves a wide range of dishes, including borscht, varenyky, shashlyk and other traditional dishes</string>
    <string name="picasso_restaurant_details">It is a restaurant specializing in European cuisine. The restaurant is located in the city center and has a refined interior. The restaurant serves a wide range of dishes, including pasta, pizza, steaks and other European dishes</string>
    <string name="cafe_kofan_details">It is a cafe specializing in European and Ukrainian cuisine. The cafe is located in the city center and has a cozy atmosphere. The cafe serves a wide range of dishes, including salads, soups, hot dishes and desserts</string>
    <string name="dao_noodle_bar_restaurant_details">It is a restaurant specializing in Asian cuisine. The restaurant is located in the city center and has a modern interior. The restaurant serves a wide variety of dishes including noodles, rice, seafood and other Asian dishes</string>
    <string name="four_seasons_restaurant_details">It is a restaurant specializing in Ukrainian cuisine. The restaurant is located in the city center and has a cozy atmosphere. The restaurant serves a wide range of dishes, including borscht, varenyky, halushki and other traditional dishes</string>
    <string name="ivushki_restaurant_work_time">11AM-10PM</string>
    <string name="picasso_restaurant_work_time">12AM-11PM</string>
    <string name="cafe_kofan_work_time">8AM-10PM</string>
    <string name="dao_noodle_bar_restaurant_work_time">10AM-10PM</string>
    <string name="four_seasons_restaurant_work_time">11AM-11PM</string>
    <string name="work_time">Work Time: %s</string>
    <string name="permanently_closed">Permanently Closed</string>
    <string name="recommendations">Recommendations</string>
    <string name="details">Details</string>
    <string name="navigate_back_arrow">Navigate back arrow</string>
    <string name="where_is_located">Where Is Located?</string>
    <string name="welcome_text">In this app you can discover the landmarks of my city</string>
    <string name="continue_text">Continue</string>
    <string name="categories_text">Categories</string>
</resources>